\land . \vdash l. \lor l. Zobyer

JUNIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER · FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

424, road 06, mirpur dohs, dhaka, Bangladesh

□ (+880) 1938033616 | ■ zobyer.ahm@gmail.com | □ zobyer | 🖹 a-h-m-zobyer | 🛅 a-h-m-zobyer-192ab2204



"I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work." Thomas A. Edison.

Summary_

Junior software engineer at Appnap Technologies Ltd. with 1.5+ years of professional experience specialized in the frontend, backend development. Loves to learn new technologies, take challenges & solve real life problems using my knowledge base. Currently searching for a software developer position where I will be able to implement my software design, development & testing knowledge to grow as a software developer.

Skills

Javascript:
Vue.js:

Python:
Nuxt.js:

Express.js:
HTML:

Django:
CSS:

FastApi:
Sql:

Work Experience_

Appnap Technologies LTD.

JUNIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER - JAVASCRIPT, VUE.JS, NUXT.JS, HTML, CSS, SASS, LARAVEL, MYSQL, GIT, JIRA

Dhaka, Bangladesh

Oct. 2021 - Ongoing

- Converted raw data from Api & database call to create effective & unique user experience in the browser.
- Built reusable components & custom library using vue.js.
- Developed Api's for frontend using Laravel.
- Integrated pusher to send & consume real time notification on both web & mobile apps from backend.
- Controlled code version & project management with agile team using git, jira.

Evident BDDhaka, Bangladesh

Junior Full Stack Developer - Python, Django, FastApi, Celery, PostgreSql, Docker, Html, Css Bulma, Laravel, PHP, Git

Jun. 2021 - Sep. 2021

- Developed multiple backend services using microservice architecture.
- Integrated amazon, ebay, woocommerce developer api's.
- Used stripe to develop payment gateway for users to subscribe to respective system.
- Implemented docker to containerize multiple application.
- · Collaborated with team members using version control systems such as git to organize modifications and assign tasks.

Projects _____

Majhi | ♀ Appnap Technologies Ltd

JAVASCRIPT, NUXT.JS, VUE.JS, HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP

2022

- Majhi is an online selling platform where any user(seller) can register and generate a online shop for his/her business.
- Developed the frontend by maintaining pixel perfection.
- Generated dynamic shop page based on the requested url(shop name).
- Built log in & registration functionality for customers using OTP verification.
- Customers can log in & place orders to a specific shop by following a few steps.
- Order page is generated dynamically for each shop which facilitates its customers to cancel & track orders.
- Multilingual(Bengali & English) features are added on all the static content of the web app.

Majhi - Admin Panel | 🚱 Appnap Technologies Ltd

JAVASCRIPT, VUE.JS, PUSHER, HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP

- By following a few steps anyone can open a digital shop.
- Seller can manage and build his own shop from this admin panel.
- Developed the frontend by maintaining pixel perfection.
- Built log in & registration functionality for customers using OTP verification.
- Sellers can track, accept & deliver any product from the admin panel.
- Pusher is integrated to display live push notification
- Multilingual(Bengali & English) features are added on all the static content of the web app. .

Manage Your E-commerce | 🚱

Evident BD

python, FastAPI, PostgreSql, Celery, Rabbitmq

2021

2022

- Three independent platforms are developed using microservice architecture..
- User can integrate & manage their amazon, ebay, woocommerce seller account using these services.
- · Amazon, ebay, woocommerce developer api's are used to communicate with respective seller accounts.
- Message broker(rabbitmq) is used to maintain steady communication between these services.
- Celery is used to carry out I/O based heavy background task using multithreading.

INVENTORY KEEPER |

Evident BD

HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP, LARAVEL, PHP, MYSQL

Jul. 2012

Integrated payment gateway(stripe) for subscribed user.developed frontend of the payment gateway.

SCHEDULED TWEET | 🚱 | 🕥

HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP, DJANGO, PYTHON, SQLITE

2022

- Twitter developer api integrated to post tweet on auhtenticated user account.
- User can schedule a tweet which will be posted automatically.

Blog Manager | 😵 Evident BD

REACT.JS, HTML,CSS, PYTHON, DJANGO

· Developed api's for blog manager to manage all blogs of evident bd.

Osmany Hall Mess Management System | 🔾 | 🔿

MIST

JAVA, HTML, CSS, SQLITE

2021

- Developed desktop app to manage & calcualte the monthly bills of the residents of MIST student dorm.
- Gmail api is integrate to send mail automatically.
- This system is developed during my academic period. MIST is currently using this system.

Problem Solving & Certificates _____

2022 Five Star Problem Solving badg, 🔾

Hackerrank

2021 SQL (Intermediate) Certificate, (2)

Hackerrank

2021 Python (Basic) Certificate, 🔾

Hackerrank

Education

Military Institute of Science & Technology(MIST)

Dhaka, Bangladesh

B. Sc. in Computer Science and Engineering

2017 - 2021

Received 200\$ for developing a student dorm management system for MIST.

Research & Paper ____

Towards Developing an Automated Attendance Management System using Fingerprint Sensor |

Dhaka, Bangladesh

2020 Emerging Technology in Computing, Communication and Electronics (ETCCE)

Jun. 2019 - Dec. 2020

• This research is conducted to develop an efficient and secure attendance system that could be beneficial for all educational institutes.

NOVEMBER 2, 2022 A. H. M. ZOBYER- RESUME 2